[AS JAR JAR BINKS]
Oh, meesa think yousa looking so, so sad.
(Leonard:)Rather than mock me...
...my friends might realize this is difficult
and try to help me through it.
(Raj:)Nope, I think mocking you is more fun.
(Howard:)Next time, don't yousa bring mama to work.
Okee-day?
(Leonard:)That was fast.
(Beverley:)Oh, the middle stall was occupied.
I'll have to try again later.
(Sheldon:)It's totally understandable.
In bladder voiding, as in real estate...
(Sheldon:)...it's location, location, location.
(Beverley:)So where were we?
(Leonard:)Howard lives with his mother and Raj can't
speak to women unless he's drunk. Go.
Oh, that's fascinating.
Selective mutism is quite rare.
(Beverley:)On the other hand, an adult Jewish male
living with his mother is so common...
...it borders on sociological cliché.
(Howard:)It's just temporary. I pay rent.